<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hong China Tea Company</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hong China Tea Company</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s the number 105 mean in Wuyi Rock tea?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/rock-tea-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/rock-tea-code/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TGY = Tie Guanyin = Iron Godness of Mercy, HJG = Huang Jin Gui&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Code&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Tea Name&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Chinese Name&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Parents&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Published Time&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;105&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Huang Guanyin&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;黄观音&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY &amp;amp; HJG&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;204&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Jin Guanyin&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;金观音&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY &amp;amp; HJG&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;101&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Yue Ming Xiang&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;悦茗香&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1994&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;304&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Dan Gui&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;丹桂&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Rou Gui&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1998&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;303&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Jiu Long Pao&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;九龙袍&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Da Hong Pao&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;301&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Chun Lan&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;春兰&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2000&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;305&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Rui Xiang&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;瑞香&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;HJG&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;203&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Jin Mu Dan&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;金牡丹&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY &amp;amp; HJG&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2003&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;402&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Huang Mei Gui&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;黄玫瑰&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;105 &amp;amp; HJG&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;210&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Zi Mei Gui&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;紫玫瑰&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY &amp;amp; HJG&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;111&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Zi Mu Dan&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;紫牡丹&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;2005&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;212&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Jin Mei Gui&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;金玫瑰&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;TGY &amp;amp; HJG&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;1990&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are connected with Wuyi Rock tea you might hear the code 105 or 305 frequently, these are the local name of tea varietal derived from the Fujian Tea Research Institute. In the process of research, a lot of options there, so a number is offered for each of them and before official published, they offer these new varietals to Wuyi farmers to try and collect feedbacks. As no name yet so the code used instead, even after published for so many years, local farmers are still more familar with these code.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Tea from China Safe? A Comprehensive Look at China&#39;s Pesticide Controls</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chinese-tea-pescides/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chinese-tea-pescides/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As a tea producer in Fujian, China, I’ve noticed frequent discussions on Reddit about the safety of Chinese tea. Many comments lack credible insights, so I aim to provide clarity based on firsthand experience. I regularly source tea from various regions and monitor industry practices closely.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Table of Contents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;History of Pesticide Use in China&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Early Stages of Reform and Opening-Up (1978–1997)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Awakening to Pesticide Risks (1997–2020)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The Rise of Natural Farming (2020–Present)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simplified Comparison of Pesticide Regulations: China vs. the U.S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Do Some Pesticides Lack MRLs in China?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;China’s Pesticide Control System&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Operating a Pesticide Shop in China&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pesticide Use Practices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tea Export Procedures from China&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unofficial Tea Grading Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;history-of-pesticide-use-in-china&#34;&gt;History of pesticide use in China&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding China’s pesticide journey requires acknowledging that progress takes time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diario</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/es/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/es/diary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-de-diciembre-de-2024-caluroso&#34;&gt;3 de diciembre de 2024 Caluroso&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/cupping-fun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;traer algunas tés para taparse con amigos&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beber solo está bien, beber juntos es genial, especialmente con personas interesantes. Hoy traje tres tés para conocer a dos personas en diferentes áreas. Un viaje de dos horas en coche no es tan largo, de hecho, conducir en las montañas es bastante divertido para mí, entenderás de qué hablo si alguna vez has conducido un coche manual.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/diary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;december-3-2024-hot&#34;&gt;December 3, 2024 Hot&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/cupping-fun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bring some teas to cup with friends&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Drinking alone is fine, drinking together is great especially with interesting people. Today I brought three teas with me to meet two people in different area. Two hours drive is not that long, actually driving in the mountains is kind of fun to me, you will understand what I talk if you ever drive manual car.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At about 10am, I arrived Luo Yan village, Mr. Lin is an old friend, he runs a big factory and his roasting skill got my respect very much. Tea cupping is fun to both of us, we headed into the cupping room, spreaded out the cupping sets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fr/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fr/diary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-décembre-2024-chaud&#34;&gt;3 décembre 2024 Chaud&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/cupping-fun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;apporter quelques thés à tasser avec des amis&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Boire seul est bien, boire ensemble est fantastique, surtout avec des personnes intéressantes. Aujourd&amp;rsquo;hui, j&amp;rsquo;ai apporté trois thés pour rencontrer deux personnes dans des domaines différents. Une conduite de deux heures, ce n&amp;rsquo;est pas si long, en fait, conduire dans les montagnes est plutôt amusant pour moi, vous comprendrez ce dont je parle si vous avez déjà conduit une voiture à boîte manuelle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tagebuch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/de/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/de/diary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-dezember-2024-heiß&#34;&gt;3. Dezember 2024 Heiß&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/cupping-fun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ein paar Tassen Tee mit Freunden trinken&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Allein trinken ist okay, zusammen trinken ist großartig, besonders mit interessanten Leuten. Heute habe ich drei Tassen Tee mitgenommen, um zwei Personen in verschiedenen Bereichen zu treffen. Zwei Stunden Autofahrt sind nicht那么长, eigentlich macht es Spaß, in den Bergen zu fahren, wenn Sie ein manuelles Auto fahren.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Um etwa 10 Uhr bin ich in Luo Yan Village angekommen, Herr Lin ist ein alter Freund, er betreibt eine große Fabrik und seine Röstfertigkeit hat mein Respekt erlangt. Tee probieren macht beiden von uns Spaß, wir gingen in die Probierecke und breiteten die Probiersets aus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>다이어리</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ko/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ko/diary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;2024년-12월-3일-더움&#34;&gt;2024년 12월 3일 더움&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/cupping-fun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;친구들과 함께 차를 마시는 모습&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;혼자 마시는 것도 좋지만, 특히 흥미로운 사람들과 함께 마시는 것은 훌륭합니다. 오늘은 세 가지 차를 가지고 다른 지역의 두 사람을 만나러 갔습니다. 두 시간 운전은 그리 길지 않았고, 사실 산길에서 수동차를 운전해 본 사람이라면 제가 말하는 것을 이해할 수 있을 겁니다.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;약 오전 10시에 뤄옌 마을에 도착했습니다. 린 씨는 오랜 친구로 대형 공장을 운영하며 그의 볶음 기술은 제가 매우 존경하는 부분입니다. 우리 둘 다 차 시음이 즐거워 곧바로 시음실로 들어가 준비를 시작했습니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>茶日記を作る</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jp/diary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jp/diary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;2024年12月3日-暑い&#34;&gt;2024年12月3日 暑い&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/cupping-fun.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;友達とカップにいくつかの紅茶を持参する&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;一人で飲むのはいいけど、面白い人と一緒に飲むのは最高だ。今日は異なる地域の2人と会うために3つの紅茶を持って行った。2時間のドライブはそれほど長くない。実は手動車を運転するのであれば、山を運転することは楽しいことだ。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;午前10時頃に羅燕村に到着し、林さんという古い友達が大きな工場を運営していて、彼の焙煎技術には私が尊敬しているものがある。紅茶の試飲は私たちにとって楽しいことだ。私たちは試飲室に向かい、試飲セットを広げ始める。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;彼の紅茶は3つの伝統的な地域のオオロン茶で、とてもきれいで、ほこりも風合いもない。彼の新しい分別機が機能していると私は思う。私が持っている3つの紅茶は：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;高焙煎の鉄観音オオロン茶&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;若葉ゴールドpeonオオロン茶&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;雲南オオロン風のプーアル茶&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;林さんが私の鉄観音に提案するのは、最初の一時間は140°Cの高温を適用し、最後の10分間は150°Cにすることだ。しかし、その高い温度では何かを燃やす可能性があるので、それを監視する人が必要です。最後の10分の焙煎後、すぐにゲートを開いて熱を放出する。ここには言葉がある：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;艺高人胆大&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;才能があるほど人間の勇気が出る&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;実際に紅茶の焙煎は最も秘密のスキルであり、焙煎前のビッグレッドローブを試したことがあれば、私の意味がわかるでしょう。焙煎は紅茶を強化したり、完全に変えることができます。オオロン茶に限らず、他の紅茶も同じです。先週私はブラックティーを焙煎して、渋みを完全に除去しました。プーアル茶も焙煎できます。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;焙煎は簡単な仕事ではなく、時間と経験だけでなく、想像力がもっと重要です。焙煎はまるで軍の将軍のように、戦場に入る前に良い戦略を必要とし、敵と自分自身を知る必要があります。どこで作られ、その紅茶の弱さと強さ、品種の性格、風土など。一旦始めると、非常に忍耐強く、30分ごとにそれを取って試飲する必要があります。昼間の電気と夜間の電気は異なるですし、異なる季節にも異なる影響があります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;それは魅力的な部分であり、他の部分は非常に少数の人々のみがこの宝石をマスターできるという点です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;工場で簡単な昼食を食べた後、私は山を下りて別の友達に会いに行ったが、残念ながら車事故が発生しました。山道は狭すぎて曲がりすぎで、ゆっくり運転すべきですが、ここでのほとんどの人々は速く運転します。2台の車が衝突し、幸いにも誰も大怪りはありませんでしたが、私たちは道路救出が道路をクリアするのを待つしかありませんでした。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ついに日がほぼ暮れるころに到着しました。座った途端、私たちは紅茶を出して始めました。私は彼の今年の秋の最高の結果を味わいましたが、とてもスムーズでした。私の紅茶の中で彼の興味を引いたのは3番目の&lt;em&gt;雲南オオロン風のプーアル茶&lt;/em&gt;でした。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;それをプーアルウーロンと呼んでおり、今年の春に雲南で作られ、60％のオオロン技術を使用し、15％のブラックティー技術を使用しましたので、他の紅茶とは一味違う風味をしています。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;プーアルウーロン&lt;/strong&gt;はオオロンの香りを持ち、ブラックティーの滑らかな口当たりとプーアルの強い体を持ちます。この紅茶は実験的なもので、私たちは来年正式に作る予定です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ブラックティーに少し手を加える。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;それは友達の叔母さんの提案です。ミスLはとても素敵な女性で、紅茶をとても愛しており、多くの紅茶山を訪れました。彼女はほとんどすべての品種を知っていますが、このような新しい友達を持つことができることを嬉しく思います。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2023年2月10日-寒い日&#34;&gt;2023年2月10日 寒い日&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;アニーと私は、彼女の中国での紅茶購入旅行について話すためにビデオ会議を設定しました。これは、彼女の会社が設立されて以来、初めて茶畑を訪れることになります。COVID-19の影響で全てが遅れましたが、幸いにも今は終わり、誰もが自由に中国に出入りできるようになりました。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私たちは、彼女が訪れたい地域や農家について話しました。わぁ、それは長いリストですね。どれだけワクワクしているかがわかります。不幸なことに、4月は私にとって非常に忙しい月なので、新しい茶葉を作らなければなりません。幸運にも、杭州の友人リリーが手を貸してくれることになったので、彼女と一緒に広東と福建に行き、その後の仕事をリリーに託す予定です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私は質問しました。「一番欲しい茶葉は何ですか？」アニーは直接答えず、毎回顧客がホワイトジェイドを買いたがるときに、彼女は「いいえ、いいえ、まずはロージェイドを試してみるべきです。これは素晴らしい女性によって生産されているんです」と言い、その女性がどのようにして人生と戦い、美を生み出したのかの話をしました。この女性の名前はミス・ジェイドです。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;アニーはこの女性を助け、彼女の茶葉をもっと広めたいと思っていますが、天候や彼女の有機農法のため、毎年高品質の茶葉を得る機会は多くありません。まるでギャンブルのようで、私たちはどちらもそれが好きではありません。さらに、それはミス・ジェイドにとって大きな損失です。この無力感は本当に嫌ですね。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2023年2月15日-まだ寒い&#34;&gt;2023年2月15日 まだ寒い&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ジェイド夫人についての最後の会話が私を悩ませています。それは日も夜も頭の中で渦巻いています。今朝5時ごろ、突然、全ての悪いことを可能な良いことに変えるアイデアが浮かんできました。アニーにテキストを送り、新しい紅茶を作る解決策が見つかったと伝えました。コストを大幅に下げながらも独特な特性を持つ一方で、品質がはるかに安定するという方案です。彼女が着陸後、もっと話すことにしました。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;この解決策が思いついた理由は？まず、ジェイド夫人がどのようにして紅茶園を運営しているか、紅茶園がどのような風景か、そして葉がどんな虫の問題を持っているかについて私は知っています。また、彼女が紅茶を作る方法についても詳しく知っています。それぞれの工程と、なぜ時々それはうまくいかないかも知っています。最も重要なのは、ジェイド夫人と私は信頼関係を持っており、彼女は私が彼女を傷つけることを提案しないと知っています。それは顔を合わせて会うことの利点であり、長年の関係を持っていることの利点でもあります。あなたは互いに頼りうる感じができます。もう1つ、私は従来の紅茶農家ではありません。私の父は建築材料ビジネスの人間です。この弱点は私に異なる視点を持っています。&lt;em&gt;古い方法&lt;/em&gt;は私を缚り付けることはできません。新しいものを創造することは素晴らしいです、自慢できるもの、他の人と共有できるものです。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私は本を読み、古い経験から学びます。私の家には本棚が3つあります。子供が1つ、妻が1つ半、残りの半分は私のもので、ほとんどの本は紅茶や歴史に関するものです。電子書籍にはまだ慣れられていません。電子書籍はすでに支払った後でも取り消されると聞いたことがあります。とにかく、ベッドのそばに本を置くことで、眠りにつけやすくなります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2023年2月20日-弱い太陽&#34;&gt;2023年2月20日 弱い太陽&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/forest-men.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;茶山でパトロール中&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;今日は月曜日です。小さな会社として、私たちは今日必ずしも会議を開催する必要がありません。なぜなら、2週間前に持ってきた紅茶を沸かして試飲しないか？テーブルには3つのロックティーと2つのブラックティーがあります。同じ有機紅茶園で作られ、異なる品種、それはどのように素敵でしょうか？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私はその茶園での経験が素晴らしかったので、大きな期待を持っています。私は昨年の10月に所有者と会いました。私たちが話した後、私たちは多くの同じ友達を持っていることに気づきました。これは私たちの間の距離をすぐに縮めました。その後、私たちは何度か連絡を取り合い、彼の紅茶園で会うことにしましたが、それは私にとって12時間のドライブが必要です。しかし、世界はあなたの望むように굴れるとは限りません。去年12月に中国はCOVID-19のゼロトレランス政策を終了し、1か月以内にほぼ全國がウイルスに感染しました。私は3日内に回復しましたが、完全に回復していない、ドラゴンさんも同様の状況です。私たちはまた来春に会うことを延期することにしました。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;2月2日に私は高速鉄道で2時間で出発し、さらに1時間のバスで、ついに周寧県に到着しました。それは冷冻人間です。同じ県内なのになぜこんなに寒いのか分かりません。バスが到着すると、ドラゴンさんがタクシーを送ってくれました。それは数時間かかると思いますが、驚いたことに、それはわずか10分で、私たちは山にいました。市中心から山までとても近いので不思議です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;もう一つの驚きはタクシー運転手からきました。彼は悪い道路を文句を言って、車のフレームにたくさん心配しています。また、二度と来ないと誓いました。まるで森を馬で走っているようです。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ついに車が止まり、私はドラゴンさんが工場の前に手を振って立っているのを見ていました。それは工場で、私は大きな建物を意味するわけではありません。主な部分は岩でできており、タイルで覆われています。50年代の伝統的な地元の建物です。多くの古いが良好に維持されている機械がそこにあります。ウィルティングマシンは台湾式で、大きくてかなり先進的です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私たちはすぐに紅茶に行き、品種、天候、労働、工芸について話し始めました。それは12時頃で少し日の光が差し始めました。家ではとても寒いです。私は携帯電話を取り出して、それは923メートルの高さを表示していました。私たちは彼の紅茶園を散策することに決めました。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;それは驚くほどに静かで、鳥のさえずり、風、葉が揺れる音だけが聞こえます。すべての紅茶園はシダの森と竹の茂みに囲まれています。まだ桜の木が咲く時期ではありませんが、地面の未知の草はすでに緑です。時々道がなくなり、私たちは森の下を通過し、茶の木の下を通り、野生のブタが作ったいくつかの小さな洞窟を通って、長い尾の鳥が近づいてきたので、飛び去りました。私は周りを見回し、南の山に凍結した滝を見つけました。ドラゴンさんは来月その音を聞くことができると言いました。私をもっと幸せにするものは、彼が植えられた品種です。合計12品種で、私は彼らが作ることができる紅茶の種類について考えています。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ドラゴンさんは別の場所に別の紅茶園を持っており、その紅茶園への道では過去に車事故が発生していました。私は谷底に残っている車を見ました。私たちはほとんど全員でホーンを鳴らしました。彼らは私にグランドカニオンの場所を示しました。ついに私たちは到着しました。失われた島、紅茶の木で。そこには4つの品種があります。清心ウーロン + 金萱 + 肉桂 + 鉄観音、全部で高級な製品を作るのに素晴らしいです。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;それは素晴らしい場所ですが、紅茶は正しいではありません。そこには多くの可能性があります。今春、私は私の紅茶作りの経験をこの土地に持ち込む予定です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2023年2月23日-暖かい太陽&#34;&gt;2023年2月23日 暖かい太陽&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/cupping-in-old-house.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;古家でのお茶試飲 with Mr. Shiny Head&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;アニーの来訪を準備するために、今日はジェイド夫人と顔を合わせる面談を決めました。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;6:20の世界はかなり違って見えます。早起きは私にとって早いですが、ベルなしで目覚めます。山の中では、街はまだあまりにも騒がしいです。ついに7時に車を運転始め、3時間半後に張憑県に到着しました。別の友達、光頭の先生も有机物質で栽培しています。私は事前に彼和他在一起2時間を計画しました。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;光頭の先生とはまだ会ったことがありませんが、すでに何年も知り合いです。彼は去年サンプルを送ってくれましたが、率直に言うと品質は低いため、今回の訪問にはあまり期待していませんでしたが、私の経験からすれば、実際に足を運ぶことで真実が異なる場合があります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私たちが出会ったのは驚きでした。私は道端に美しい伝統的な家を見たくて、車を運転して近づいてみたとき、別の家から男性が現れ、私がホンであるかどうか尋ねました。私はそうだと言って、その男性が光頭の先生であるかもしれないと気づきました。そして彼は自分のナンバープレートから私を認識したと説明しました。彼は友人の家に足を運んで紅茶を飲みに誘いました。私は2人の他の友達が古いではなく、中年の人であることに嬉しくなりました。後で別の中年の男性が入ってきましたが、なぜ私が嬉しくなりますか？若さはエネルギーを意味し、この業界が家に若い人を引き戻すことができることを意味し、この業界は未来があることを意味します。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ピーナッツと紅茶のカップの後、私たちは光頭の先生の工場を訪れることに決めました。私は車を降りて彼の馬に乗りました。光頭の先生の紅茶園は村の最奥に位置しており、他の場所から遠く離れています。これは有机物質農業の最初の保護です。次に彼は私を彼の工場と紅茶園を案内しました。彼が有机物質を選択した理由を教えて、そして土を見せました。通常、私が紅茶園で最初に見る場所は植物や草や花ではなく、土です。それは硬化しているか、緩いかを見ます。良い土は良い生活サイクルを意味し、微生物、ミミズなどです。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私はそこに設置されている給水システムを見て嬉しかったですが、彼は去年それが機能しなかったと言いました。水は頂部から来るのですが、去年は頂部でさえ水がなく、それはひどい干旱の年でした。私も紅茶園でいくつかの鶏を見かけました。彼はそれはすぐに出産する娘のためにあると言いました。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;驚くべきことに、彼は彼の間違いの1つを見せてくれました。それは彼が紅茶を植える方法です。紅茶の植物は線を並べて坐っていますが、その線は垂直です。それが水平であれば、土の流出による損失を防ぐのに役立ちます。そして、彼はプロで運営されている別の有机物質紅茶会社から学び続けています。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;この談話の後、私は彼がオープンマインドな男性であり、何かを共有し、議論できると感じました。私は去年彼から送られた悪いサンプルをmentionし、有机物質が通常品質が低いことを始め話題にしました。特にオオロン茶の場合。これが真実です。市場では、一般的なものは良い香りを持ち、ずっと良い品質を持ちますが、逆に彼の有机物質ガーデンはただの悪い香りの紅茶しか生成しませんし、時には受ける価格は一般的な紅茶よりも低いです。高い香りは紅茶の販売の第一優先事項ですが、私たちはともに同意しましたが、通常の工芸は有机物質を弱くします。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私は彼に、有机物質の葉材料の利点を利用して他の香りを得るための2つの他の工芸を共有しました。通常の工芸が作成する香りではなく、果物の香り、蜂蜜の香り、 심지어 焙煎의香气、光頭の先生はかなり興味を持ちました。多分このオープンな談話のせいで、彼は私に彼の別の古い木の紅茶園をツアーするよう提案しました。それは50年以上放置されていましたが、彼はそれを回復しました。もちろん私は興味がありますので、私たちは別の登山を取りましたし、私はいくつかのミルクボックスに気づきました。彼はそれは紅茶の木のために使用され、彼は本物のミルクを使用して紅茶を命を回復させたと言いました。それは馬鹿げてそうですが、彼の紅茶の心はどれだけ熱いですか！&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apprendre le thé blanc à la difficile</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fr/learn-white-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:28:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fr/learn-white-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Le thé blanc est un peu de l&amp;rsquo;ouest sauvage pour la plupart des gens, il a des caractères charmants très spéciaux qui attendent d&amp;rsquo;être découverts. C&amp;rsquo;est un thé facile à préparer, pas de soucis d&amp;rsquo;amertume quel que soit la température ou le temps d&amp;rsquo;infusion appliqués, et il semble également facile à produire, seulement deux étapes, Flétrissement et Séchage. En réalité, c&amp;rsquo;est un thé dangereux, simple n&amp;rsquo;est pas facile pour tout le monde. Espérons que ce «Apprendre le thé blanc à la difficile» peut rendre votre voyage du thé blanc se déroule sans heurt.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aprende el té blanco de la manera difícil</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/es/learn-white-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:28:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/es/learn-white-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;El té blanco es como el lejano oeste para la mayoría de las personas, tiene caracteres encantadores muy especiales que esperan ser descubiertos. Es un té fácil de preparar, no hay preocupaciones de amargura sin importar la temperatura o el tiempo de infusión aplicados, y también parece fácil de producir, solo dos pasos, Descanso y Secado. En realidad, es un té peligroso, simple no es fácil para todos. Esperemos que este &amp;ldquo;Aprende el té blanco de la manera difícil&amp;rdquo; pueda hacer que tu viaje con el té blanco sea suave.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn White Tea The Hard Way</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/learn-white-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:28:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/learn-white-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;White tea is kind of wild western to most people, it has very special charming characters that waiting for discovery. It&amp;rsquo;s an easy tea to brew, no worries of bitterness no matter what temperature or steeping time applied, also it sounds easy to produce too, just two steps, Withering and Drying. Actually it&amp;rsquo;s an dangerous tea, simple is not easy for all. Hopefully this Learn White Tea The Hard Way can get your White tea journey go smoothly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lernen Sie Schwarzen Tee auf der schwierigen Weise</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/de/learn-white-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:28:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/de/learn-white-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Der Weißtee ist für die meisten Menschen ein bisschen Wild West, er hat sehr besondere charmante Charaktere, die auf Entdeckung warten. Es ist ein einfaches Tee, das Brauen, keine Bedenken hinsichtlich Bitterkeit egal welche Temperatur oder Infusion Zeit angewendet wird, und es klingt auch einfach herzustellen, nur zwei Schritte, Welzen und Trocknen. Tatsächlich ist es ein gefährlicher Tee, einfach ist nicht einfach für alle. Hoffentlich kann dieser &amp;ldquo;Learn White Tea The Hard Way&amp;rdquo; Ihren Weißtee-Reise glatt laufen lassen.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ホワイトティーをハードウェイで学ぶ</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jp/learn-white-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 08:28:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jp/learn-white-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ホワイトティーはほとんどの人々にとってワイルドウエスタンのようなもので、待ち望まれる非常に特別な魅力的な特性があります。それは Brewing が簡単な紅茶で、どのような温度や浸出時間を適用しても苦味の心配はありません。また、生産も簡単そうですし、ウィルティングとドライングの2つのステップだけで済みます。実際にはそれは危険な紅茶で、誰にとっても簡単ではありません。うまくいけば、この「ホワイトティーをハードウェイで学ぶ」はあなたのホワイトティーの旅を順調に行かせることができます。&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/two-white-teas.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Two White teas&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;目次&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第一部分&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ホワイトティーの色は白ですか？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;シルバーニードル 女王様&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ホワイトピーオニー 王子様&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ゴングメイ アポロン&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ショウメイ アテナ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第二部分&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;6&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;自分の紅茶を年齢を重ねるべきです&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;手作り神話&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;紅茶は野生を呼ぶ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;包括的 vs. 強力&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;農薬には歴史があります&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;第三部分&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol start=&#34;11&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;孤独なマスター・ファンショウロン&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;有機大使シェロンウェイ&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ホワイトティーの色は白ですか&#34;&gt;ホワイトティーの色は白ですか？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ホワイトティーを学ぶ最初のことは、定義についてです。ホワイトティーは市場の小さな兄弟のようなもので、製品は多くなく、情報もあまり手に入りません。中国には、GB/T 22291-2017番号のホワイトティーの国家标准があります。多くの質問に答えることができます。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;gbt-22291-2017&#34;&gt;GB/T 22291-2017&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;実際には、この基準の草案単位についての興味深い部分であり、それがどこから来るかを示しています。10つの単位があります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.co-tea.com&#34;&gt;杭州茶研究所&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;福建裕荣香茶有限公司&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;富品質測定テスト研究所&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pinpinxiang.cn&#34;&gt;福建品品茶有限公司&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.lvxueyatea.com&#34;&gt;福建天湖茶业有限公司&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;政和白牡丹茶业有限公司&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;政和道香茶业有限公司&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.fafu.edu.cn&#34;&gt;福建农林大学&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://teatesting.co-tea.com&#34;&gt;国家茶品質検査テストセンター&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ctma.com.cn&#34;&gt;中国茶マーケティング協会&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;上記の10つの単位は3つのグループに分類できます。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;8番のように大学&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;2番、4-7番のように私立茶会社&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;1番、3番、9番、10番のように国家機関&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;すべての私立茶会社は福建省出身で、4番と大学も含め、主に基準を定義しています。福建はホワイトティーの中心地で、特に&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.fdbaicha.com&#34;&gt;福鼎&lt;/a&gt;市は中国のホワイトティーの中心です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;ホワイトティーの定義&#34;&gt;ホワイトティーの定義&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GB/T 22291-2017法案では、ホワイトティーについて明確な言葉があります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ホワイトティーは、Camellia Sinensisの芽、葉、または若い茎から作られ、ウィルティング、ドライング、そしてリフィNINGのプロセスを経ます。&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;この技術の最も重要な部分はウィルティングまたは長期のウィルティングで、ここでは&lt;strong&gt;発酵&lt;/strong&gt;という言葉は使われませんが、少し発酵します。ブラックティーの発酵には高い温度と高い湿度が必要ですので、3-5時間で激しく赤色に変わります。逆にホワイトティーは48-72時間以上かかり、ずっと長いショットで、そこで描写的な言葉&lt;em&gt;微妙&lt;/em&gt;が使われます。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;色&#34;&gt;色&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ホワイトティーには4つのタイプがあります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;シルバーニードル - Bai Hao Yin Zhen 白毫银针&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ホワイトピーオニー - Bai Mu Dan 白牡丹&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ゴングメイ - Gong Mei 贡眉&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;ショウメイ - Shou Mei 寿眉&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;色を説明するために使用される言葉には、銀、灰、白、緑が含まれます。&lt;em&gt;ロングブロウ&lt;/em&gt;にはブラックも使われますが、&lt;em&gt;ホワイト&lt;/em&gt;が最も頻繁に使われる言葉です。だからもし望むなら、ホワイトティーは白だと任意に言うことができます。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deutsche Höchstgrenzen für Pestizidrückstände auf chinesischem Tee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/de/de-mrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/de/de-mrl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Als professioneller Exporteur ist die Bewältigung der Höchstgrenzen für Pestizidrückstände der erste Schritt, um Ihnen Tee anzubieten. Deutschland hat andere Anforderungen als die USA. Für uns ist es das Gleiche, da das, was die Hong China Tea Company anbietet, Tee ohne Pestizide ist, der den Standards jedes Landes entspricht. Die getesteten Tees umfassen Tieguanyin, Wuyi-Felstee, Puertee, Weißtee und Schwarztee, sogar Jasmintee.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Der herausforderndste Tee ist definitiv Oolong, egal ob Tieguanyin oder Wuyi Da Hong Pao, da Oolong reifes Blätter und nicht kleine Knospen benötigt. Das Wachsen von Knospen zu Blättern dauert über 20 Tage und diese lange Zeit bietet Insekten die Möglichkeit, insbesondere bei steigender Temperatur, eine höhere Temperatur bedeutet mehr Insekten. Wenn das Blatt zur richtigen Zeit für die Oolong-Pflücke reif ist, ist es ziemlich schwer, es intakt zu halten, wenn es von Schädlingen umgeben ist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU/UK MRL</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/eu-mrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/eu-mrl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a professional exporter, conquering the Maximum Residue Limit is the first step to offer you teas. EU/UK has different requirements from USA. To us, it&amp;rsquo;s the same, as what Hong China Tea Company offer is Pesticide Free tea which can conform to any countries&amp;rsquo; standard. The tested teas including Tieguanyin, Wuyi Rock tea, Puer, White tea and Black tea even Jasmine tea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most challenging tea is definitely Oolong, no matter Tieguanyin or Wuyi Da Hong Pao, as what Oolong requires is mature leaf instead of little buds, growing from buds into leaf needs over 20 days and that long time gives insects chance especially under the also growing temperature, higher temperature means more insects. When the leaf is at the right time for Oolong picking, it&amp;rsquo;s quite hard to keep it intact when bad guys surrounded.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limite maximale de résidus de pesticides français sur le thé chinois</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/fr/fr-mrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/fr/fr-mrl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;En tant que professionnel exportateur, maîtriser la limite maximale de résidus (MRL) est la première étape pour vous offrir des thés. La France a des exigences différentes des États-Unis. Pour nous, c&amp;rsquo;est la même chose, car ce que l&amp;rsquo;entreprise de thé Hong China Tea propose est un thé sans pesticide qui peut se conformer aux normes de tous les pays. Les thés testés incluent Tieguanyin, le thé de roche Wuyi, le puér, le thé blanc et le thé noir, voire le thé à la jasmin.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Límites Máximos de Residuos (MRL) de la UE/RU</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/es/es-mrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/es/es-mrl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Como exportador profesional, dominar los Límites Máximos de Residuos es el primer paso para ofrecerte té. La UE/RU tiene requisitos diferentes a los de EE. UU. Para nosotros, es lo mismo, ya que lo que ofrece la Compañía de Té Hong China es té sin pesticidas que puede cumplir con los estándares de cualquier país. Los tés probados incluyen Tieguanyin, té de roca Wuyi, Puer, té blanco y té negro, incluso té de jazmín.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>한국 MRL에 대한 차</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ko/ko-mrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ko/ko-mrl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;전문적인 수출업자로서, 최대잔류기준(MRL)을征服하는 것이 여러분에게 차를 제공하는 첫걸음입니다. 한국의 요구사항은 미국과 다르지만, 우리에게는 똑같습니다. 홍콩 중국 차 회사가 제공하는 것은農藥무农药차로 어떤国家标准에도 맞는 것입니다. 검사에 통과한 차에는Tieguanyin(티구안음), Wuyi Rock tea 산 암차(우이산 엥차), 푸얼 차(푸에르 차), 백차(백차), 홍차(홍차) 심지어 재스민 차(재스민 차)도 포함됩니다.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;가장 도전적인 차는 분명히乌龙茶이며, Tieguanyin이나 Wuyi Da Hong Pao를 막론하고, 乌龙茶가 필요로 하는 것은 성숙한 잎이 아니라 작은 싹입니다. 싹에서 잎으로 성장하는 데는 20일이 넘게 걸리며 그 긴 시간이 곧昆虫에게 기회를 줍니다. 특히 성장하는 온도가 높을수록 昆虫이 많습니다. 잎이 乌龙茶 뽑기에 적당한 시기이면, 나쁜 녀석들이 둘러싸였을 때 그것을 무사히 유지하는 것이 매우 어렵습니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>中国茶に適用される日本の最大農薬残存量制限</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jp/jp-mrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jp/jp-mrl/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;プロフェッショナルな輸出業者として、最大残存量制限を克服することは、お茶を提供する最初のステップです。日本はUSAとは異なる要件を持っています。私たちにとっては同じです。なぜなら、中国紅茶会社が提供するのは、どの国の基準にも適合できる無農薬の紅茶です。テストされた紅茶には、鉄観音、武夷岩茶、プーアル茶、白茶、ブラック茶、ジャスミン茶が含まれます。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;最も挑戦的な紅茶は間違いなくオオロン茶です。鉄観音や武夷大紅袍を問わず、オオロン茶が必要なのは成熟した葉で、小さな芽ではありません。芽から葉に成長するのに20日以上かかりますし、その長時間は特に温度が上昇するにつれて昆虫にチャンスを与えます。オオロン茶の収穫の適時が来たら、悪い奴らに囲まれている時にそれを無傷に保つことは非常に困難です。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;私たちに驚きを与えるものは、アントラキノンとマトリンです。アントラキノンは新しい汚染物で、未知の源で、実際には農薬ではないのに世界中で茶に発生しています。マトリンは、伝統的な中国医学のSophora flavescens Aitonから分離されたアルカロイドで、簡単に言えば、自然の植物ベースの虫歯です。いくつかの農夫はこのマトリンを有機農業の練習で農薬の自然な代替品として扱っています。しかしルールはルールです。ここでは正しいか間違っているかについて議論するのではありません。私たちはここでルールに適合するベストソリューションを見つけるためにいます。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;もう一点はテストラボについてです。異なるラボは異なる能力を持っており、数十年にわたって良い評判の&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eurofins.com&#34;&gt;Eurofins&lt;/a&gt;と協力してきました。SGSも大丈夫ですが、それは消費者にとってもっと有名です。一方、Eurofinsは紅茶の輸入者/輸出者にとってもっと有名です。下に、今週受け取ったオオロン茶のテスト報告書があります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;いつも無農薬でいることの方法は&#34;&gt;いつも無農薬でいることの方法は？&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;これは賢明な質問です。実際にあなたと私たちが望むのは報告書ではなく、安全な製品であり、それだけではなく、最初の日から最後の日までです。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;また、テストを行う時、提供するサンプルはすべての茶園をカバーすることはできませんし、茶園は非常に大きくなることがあります。あなたが持っているものは特定の地域から来るかもしれませんが、どうやってあなたが持っているサンプルが全体の茶園を代表できるかを確かめればいいですか？&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;通常、私は5つの面をチェックします：&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;茶園には草がありますか？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;土は緩いか硬いか？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;葉は黄緑色か暗緑色か？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;収穫者はそれについて何と言いますか？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;所有者の隣人は何と言いますか？&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;すべてが良好であれば、無農薬は注文だけではなく、すべての従業員とコミュニティによって受け入れられたアイデアです。すべてがフラッシュアウトするかもしれませんが、偉大な思想だけが生き残ります。&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/oolong-testing-report.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Hong China Tea CompanyのTieguanyinオオロン茶テスト報告書&#34; title=&#34;EurofinsによるTieguanyin茶テスト報告書&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to find Pesticide Free tea in China?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/pesticide-free-tea-sourcing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/pesticide-free-tea-sourcing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Seeking excellence means choosing to forge your own sword to cut through the limitations of your life.” – James A. Murphy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This week in the Throne and Beauty teayard of Fujian Province, I take off the handcuffs of White tea processing, to use mature tea leaf instead of traditionally applied young leaf, finally made a surprisingly nice White tea, not just about the versatile and charming aroma, even not the silky mouthfeel, only the rebellious profile can shine the eyes. The tea is simply called &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.chinabeastsandlegends.com/bai-long-ma&#34;&gt;White Dragon Horse&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions on Organic tea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ten-questions-on-organic-tea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ten-questions-on-organic-tea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;contents&#34;&gt;Contents&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is Organic more healthy?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s real Organic?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Does Organic tea taste better?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to find Chinese Organic tea farmers?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between Organic and Pesticide Free?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which lab should be used for Organic tea testing?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Does small farmer have better organic tea?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Should Organic tea be more expensive?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Does pest bitten means Organic?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Why does some Pesticide Free teas not Organic certified?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Last Question: Which tea to buy? Pesticide Free or Organic?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple roasting guide for Oolong tea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/roast-oolong/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/roast-oolong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;First question is why need roasting? The answer is the direction for howto roast it. Normally there are two circumstances, stale or quality not ideal. Let&amp;rsquo;s go straight to the point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;stale-tea-roasting&#34;&gt;Stale tea roasting&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I quite like an analogy, that tea is kind of human being. If you stay in home and do not do any excise, your body gonna lose the intensity and flabby, that&amp;rsquo;s the same with tea, the weak defense will be easily broken through especially the unwelcome other smells, so your tea doesn&amp;rsquo;t smell clean anymore.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jasmine tea history - stories, crafts and factories</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/jasmine-tea-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/jasmine-tea-history/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There are many articles available online about history of Jasmine tea if you Google, then why another post? The simple answer is I want to offer something that is useful for importers&amp;rsquo; tea purchasing decision, so common consumers can have more chance to buy good quality tea.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/jasmine-teas.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Jasmine tea families&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;where-is-the-jasmine-tea-factory&#34;&gt;Where is the jasmine tea factory?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Factory Location&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Rate&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;Remarks&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Heng County of Guangxi&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;75%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;96000tons&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Fuzhou city of Fujian&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;8.6%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;11000tons&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Qianwei County of Sichuan&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;10.9%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;14000tons&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Yuanjiang county of Yunnan&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;5.5%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;7000tons&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Above data is originated from the &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.ctma.com.cn&#34;&gt;China Tea Marketing Association&lt;/a&gt; in 2021, so that&amp;rsquo;s the latest analytics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>재스민 차의 역사 - 이야기, 공예, 그리고 공장</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/ko/jasmine-tea-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/ko/jasmine-tea-history/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;구글에서 검색하면 재스민 차 역사에 관한 많은 글이 있지만, 왜 또 다른 글을 작성할까요? 간단한 답변은 수입업자의 차 구매 결정에 도움이 되는 정보를 제공하여 일반 소비자들이 더 좋은 품질의 차를 구매할 기회를 늘리기 위함입니다.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/jasmine-teas.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;재스민 차 가족들&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;재스민-차-공장은-어디에-있을까요&#34;&gt;재스민 차 공장은 어디에 있을까요?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;공장 위치&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;비율&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;비고&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;광시성 헝 현&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;75%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;96,000톤&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;푸젠성 푸저우 시&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;8.6%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;11,000톤&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;쓰촨성 첸웨이 현&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;10.9%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;14,000톤&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;윈난성 위안장 현&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;5.5%&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;7,000톤&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;위 데이터는 2021년 &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.ctma.com.cn&#34;&gt;중국 차 마케팅 협회&lt;/a&gt;에서 제공한 것으로 최신 분석 자료입니다.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where China tea will go?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/china-tea-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/china-tea-trend/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;China is the origin of tea and after thousands years of development, it becomes what we see now, six tea types inculding Black tea, Green tea, White tea, Oolong tea, Yellow tea, Dark tea and almost all 34 provinces produce tea. Open &lt;a href=&#34;http://cypt.ahbd.net/#/Index&#34;&gt;Anhui Tea Map&lt;/a&gt; and click any flag on the map you will get detailed introduction of a famous tea in Anhui province, you might get shocked how could it be possible that so many teas available there, and that&amp;rsquo;s just in one province, but definitely yes that&amp;rsquo;s true. So why so many teas?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to source China tea during lockdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/tea-sourcing-during-lockdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/tea-sourcing-during-lockdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tea sourcing is funny but a lot of challenges especially right now the world still has COVID-19 virus, all travel are severely restricted, even already have vaccinated, it&amp;rsquo;s not 100% safe, for your safety it&amp;rsquo;s better to stay where you are, besides the plane ticket is crazy expensive, then how to get the tea sourcing job done?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note suggestions proposed below might be workable only in China.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-options-for-tea-sourcing&#34;&gt;3 Options for Tea Sourcing&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Directly work with tea farmer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Partner with a tea broker&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Buy from trading company&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not anyone option is perfect, all have advantage and disadvantage, with farmer you can get the freshest tea and background stories but no QC, no shipping service, payment might be problem too and normally each farmer just make one tea, if you offer many teas then you need talk to many farmers, that&amp;rsquo;s a lot of work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to import China teas into USA – v0.5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2019-10-17-tea-import-howto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2019-10-17-tea-import-howto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tea is getting more and more popular in America, according to the statistics published by  &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.teausa.org&#34;&gt;Tea Association of USA&lt;/a&gt;, so it’s a good time to jump into the tea business. There are so many teas available. You can buy tea from a domestic wholesaler or from the origin directly for some real benefits. Although it’s a little complex to deal with importing business, here is some guidance to help you make the task easier.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shoot a good tea picture in 10 minutes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/picture-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 16:53:55 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/picture-shooting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;summary&#34;&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This short manual shows you how to shoot a simple yet clean picture for teas in unprofessional way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;equipments&#34;&gt;Equipments&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A SLR camera like Canon 500D&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A good lens like Canon EF 50mm&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A tripod&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;pre-shooting-preparation&#34;&gt;Pre-shooting preparation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Pick CDR (raw) format for camera storage, so can have more possibilities for adjustment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Choose a good day with sunshine or you will need extra lights&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A4 white paper as background&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Tea (&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/&#34;&gt;contact Daniel&lt;/a&gt; if you need a good one)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;shooting-technique&#34;&gt;Shooting technique&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Turn to M: Manual Mode on cameral&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set ISO: 100&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set diaphragm: f 6.3&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set shutter: 1/5&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more explanations of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://camera-wiki.org/wiki/Diaphragm&#34;&gt;Diaphragm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://camera-wiki.org/wiki/Shutter_speed&#34;&gt;Shutter Speed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, please refer to &lt;a href=&#34;https://electronics.howstuffworks.com/camera4.htm&#34;&gt;How Cameras Work&lt;/a&gt;. In short, picture shooting is a light controlling game, both Diaphragm and Shutter can do it in different way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tea Wholesale Catalog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/catalog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2019 10:54:42 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/catalog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;OOLONG TEA&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;BLACK TEA&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;YUNNAN PUER&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;GREEN &amp;amp; JASMINE TEA&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#1&#34;&gt;#7276 Huang Jin Gui&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#21&#34;&gt;#5176 Wild Wulong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#8275 Yiwu Puerh&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#9150 Long Jing&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#2&#34;&gt;#7274 Classic Tieguanyin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#22&#34;&gt;#5177 Tiger Mountain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#8175 Broken Silver&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#9375 Anji Bai Cha&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#3&#34;&gt;#7176 Green Tieguanyin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#23&#34;&gt;#5275 Red Fairie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#8276 Nanluo Raw Puer&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#9485 Green Mist&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#4&#34;&gt;#7175 High Oxidization TGY&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#5300 Jin Junmei&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#8277 Pasha Raw Puer&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#9484 Green Arrow&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#5&#34;&gt;#7378 Classic Dahongpao&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#5375 Wuyi Lapsang&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#8278 Pasha Raw Puer&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#9154 Duyun Fishhook&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#6&#34;&gt;#7575 Fairie Diamond&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#5477 Honey Dancong&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#8375 Puer Tuo Cha&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#9994 Organic Matcha&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#7&#34;&gt;#7675 Pinho White Bud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#5375 Yunnan Tip&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#37&#34;&gt;#8378 Classic Ripe Puer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;#9677 Snow Bitter&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;oolong-tea&#34;&gt;OOLONG TEA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to Chinese Tea Classification, semi-oxidized is Oolong. The higheset oxidization Oolong is Oriental Beauty, the lowest oxidization Oolong is a mistery yet.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Taste Good</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/small-taste-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 22:05:07 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/small-taste-good/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The genesis of all is a special tea travel in 2019, we two men drove a car all around the tea production area, we made some reviews on farmers, one very interesting idea we got is &lt;strong&gt;quantity does matter quality&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nowadays it is impossible to follow the same process as in the past because of the large quantity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s what we heard from a 83 years old tea man and similar saying from other farmers. No pay no get, that&amp;rsquo;s quite reasonable, especially when dealing with food or tea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howto Source Tea in China</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/howto-source-tea-in-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 10:01:50 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/howto-source-tea-in-china/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn’t do than by the ones you did do. So throw off the bowlines. Sail away from the safe harbor. Catch the trade winds in your sails. Explore. Dream. Discover.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;-Mark Twain&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a tea enthusiast and buyer, getting as close as possible to the source could be benefit to your business very much, four points in my head now:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-Secret Hidding China Tea Purchasing Tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/purchasing-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 13:26:21 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/purchasing-tour/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/wild-away-593531-unsplash.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Tea adventure&#34; title=&#34;Photo by Wild &amp;amp; Away on Unsplash&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a serial post, today is part one, few days later we will have this kind of purchasing tour and publish part two.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a tea maker, certified tea master and tea lover, the greatest meaning for me is more and more people can get good tea, but the real world is not the same as what we want, you can easily find a lot incorrect information on the web, the tea you buy could be very likely not good, and still possibly you are not aware of all this wrong.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spicy Wulong - A New Chapter of Oolong tea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/spicy-wulong/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 21:07:15 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/spicy-wulong/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/spicy-wulong.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Spicy Wulong tea&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-spicy&#34;&gt;Why Spicy?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Firstly to clarify a possible misunderstanding, this tea is 100% natural, not scented with jinger or chilli, it&amp;rsquo;s a pure loose leaf tea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s made with varietal of Yellow Dawn and Iron Godness of Mercy, floral, sweet and a slightly strong sense of irritation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-result-of-3-yrs-of-experiment&#34;&gt;A Result of 3 yrs of experiment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oolong tea is a complex tea, we love it so much, so maybe to show out our love is to make an easy yet affordable tea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2018 China Spring Tea Report</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-spring-tea-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 May 2018 11:07:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/2018-spring-tea-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today the God&amp;rsquo;s generous is over, standing in the room, the raining sounds like one thousand bulls are kicking the drum, no sun no good tea, but I can see vegetables, rice and trees are sucking the sweet dew so greedily, I can say no more than thanks, so generously the spring tea season is over, let&amp;rsquo;s walk through what tea we get, this report will not looks like a &lt;em&gt;report&lt;/em&gt;, it&amp;rsquo;s just based on the farmers I talked to, the mountain my feet trod.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First thing first, how is the quality and price? the answer is quite simple, better and higher, I will explain the reason later.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Tea Sourcing Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/white-tea-sourcing-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 07:16:39 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/white-tea-sourcing-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/white-tea-map.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;White tea map&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A map means a lot to an adventure, a map with direction leading sometimes is more valuable than a map with all details. Above map was made in 1963 by Zhang Tianfu, this map shows three most important white tea production areas: Fuding, Zheng He and Jian Yang.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Theoretically “white” is just about processing craft, all tea varieties can be made into White, just like all people can sing doesn’t mean everyone can be a singer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Huang Jin Gui - A Fxxking Good Aroma Oolong tea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/huangjingui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/huangjingui/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/picking.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;leaf&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Huang Jin Gui (aka Jade Oolong) is an incredible tea from Anxi county of Fujian China, it&amp;rsquo;s the only tea honored by the woman, a woman named Wang Dan who introduced this varietal to the world in 1860.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jin Junmei -  A New Legend of Wuyi Black tea</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/jinjunmei/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/jinjunmei/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wuyi Jin Jun Mei opened a new world for black tea in China, you can not imagine black tea can be so gorgeous so noble before. It was June 2005, under several Beijing customers&amp;rsquo; proposal, a team grouped up and finally successfully created Jin Jun Mei black tea.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Daniel has been my supplier for Fujian teas since 2012 and more recently my advisor and friend. Perhaps the easiest way of explaining why I trust him is that the two teas of his which I entered for the UK Great Taste Awards this year both won Triple Gold .”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;- Mr. Cris Martindale, Owner of Caffi Cristobal, UK&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Tea Fishman is a small Israeli tea importer and we are happy to cooperate with Hong China Tea Company. The care and the respect, we have gotten from this company, is highly appreciated. We recommend this company for all it may concern. ”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Tea Tour</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teatour/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teatour/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tea-tours-the-best-way-to-experience-our-authentic-tea-culture&#34;&gt;Tea tours: the best way to experience our authentic tea culture&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I had a fabulous experience in Fujian Province with my Tea Tour arranged by World Tea Tours and guided in Xiamen by Daniel Hong.  We visited Anxi County and were received warmly by local tea producers. I don&amp;rsquo;t think we could ever hope to have such unique and valuable tea experiences as we had with Daniel guiding us. &amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/daniel-hong.png&#34; alt=&#34;Photo of Daniel Hong&#34; style=&#34;float: left;&#34; /&gt;  &#xA;CEO Mr. Daniel Hong  &#xA;– founder and owner, Tea Master  &#xA;Phone: (+86) 592-837-6662  &#xA;E-mail: daniel@hongchinatea.com      &#xA;**Company address:**  &#xA;Hong China Tea Company  &#xA;No. 1028 Lvling Road  &#xA;Xiamen, Fujian Province 361009 China&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/img/k-kristensen.png&#34; alt=&#34;Photo of Kenneth Kristensen&#34; style=&#34;float: left;&#34; /&gt;  &#xA;Business Consultant Mr. Kenneth Kristensen  &#xA;– Special assistant to the CEO  &#xA;E-mail:   &#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-partners-in-the-world&#34;&gt;Our Partners in the World&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Here is a list of tea merchants who have been our partner, if you ever need a second opinion, just ask anyone who has been our guest &amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
